Unspeakable Human Suffering and Torture... All in the name of Medical Research.
Dr. Rage is a horror film directed by Jeff Broadstreet.
After enrolling in an experimental study on Rage Impulse Disorder at the Straun
Foundation, Michael Dare discovers that the research is not what it seems.
After learning that the Foundation's head, Dr.
Timothy Straun has his own agenda for them, Dare and head resident Dr.
Susan Verger team up to stop him.
Straun's shocking family secret and twisted plan are
then revealed in a stunning finale.
Dr. Timothy Straun, played by Andrew Divoff.
Dr. Susan Verger, played by Denice Duff.
Michael Dare, played by Stephen Polk.
Molly, played by Karen Black.
Moe Moebius, played by John Kassir.
Junior, played by Robert DiTillio.
Robin Yvette Allen (born February 6, 1968), known professionally as The Lady of Rage, is an American rapper, singer and
actress best known for her collaborations with several other Death Row Records artists, including Dr.
Dre and Snoop Dogg on the seminal albums, The Chronic and Doggystyle.
The Lady of Rage has been described as "one of the most skillful female
MCs" with a "mastery of flow" and "hard-core lyrics".
The tone is dark and mind_bending.